ARUSHA SHARMA

Pre-Final year Engineering student having interest in Web Development. Having knowledge of programming languages like C++, Java, Html, CSS, JavaScript, Express.js, MongoDB. Made webpages and worked on projects with the same. Also have worked in teams. Looking forward to explore more in frontend as well as backend development.

LinkedIn Id

https://www.linkedin.com/in/arusha-sharma-6ab1031b0/

Gmail

@arusha.sharma2001@gmail.com

Phone No.

7276069505

SKILLS AND PROFICIENCIES

- C++, Java, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, NodeJS, SQL, Express.js, MongoDB, Canva.
- Leadership, teamwork, multitasking, problem solving skills, and attention to detail.
- Software and web development.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

B.E. (ENTC) - 9.4 CGP

Sinhgad College Of Engineering, Pune (2019-Present)

Higher Secondary - 83%

Sardar Dastur Hormazdiar Junior College, Pune (HSC 2017-2019)

Secondary - 89%

Joseph's Convent School, Pune (SSC 2007-2017)

WORK HISTORY

Content Team Head - Quantum Magazine

Sinhgad College of Engineering | Sep 2021 - Present

- Managing and working with the team to get effective articles.
- Interviewed college clubs.
- Worked on articles related to recent technologies.

Executive Team Member - CodeChef SCOE Chapter

Sinhgad College of Engineering Aug 2021 - Present

- Working with the team to conduct events and contests among the community.
- Organised and took part as a speaker for sessions and explained data structure concepts.
- Worked with the social media team in expanding our community.

Software Developer Intern-Stige

Aug 2021 - Sept 2021

- Worked with HTML, CSS and JavaScript for frontend and learning to make responsive webpages
- Working with NodeJS, Express.js and MongoDB for backend and building projects using the same.

PROJECTS

Webpages

- Made a responsive Swiggy Website page clone using technologies like HTML, CSS and JavaScript.
- Made a Frontend Portfolio Project- Netflix website consisting of Landing page, Sign-in/Sign-up Page and Browser page clone.
- Made a Drumkit webpage (produces different sounds on clicking different letters).